freewebsite.com 2013-03-12

# FreeWebsite.com Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, communicate and disclose, and make use of personal information that you provide on our Web site.

Other than as described in this Policy, we will not give any information about you to others without your express permission.

Information collected includes your name, address, telephone number, and email address. We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. 

Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up to date. 

We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide services to us.

We may use your information to present a co-branded offer with our partners or affiliates. If we collect information from you in connection with a co-branded offer, it will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the information and whose privacy statement applies.

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect our property and rights or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. We will also share your information to the extent necessary to comply with ICANN's rules, regulations and policies.

We use cookies to ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads.

We use emails to communicate with you, confirm your placed order, and to send information that you have requested. We also provide email links, to allow you to contact us directly. This information you send us may be stored and used to improve this Site, and our products, or it may be reviewed and discarded. If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please let us know by contacting us at support [@] freewebsite.com

You may alter your account information or opt out of receiving communications from us and our partners at any time. We have the following options for changing and modifying your account information or contact preferences.

  * Mail us at: FreeWebsite.com  
Attn: Account Manager  
1230 Avenue of the Americas  
Rockefeller Center, 7th Floor  
New York, NY 10020
  * Call us at: 1-800-591-1904

The security of your personal information is important to us. This Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on out order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submit to us with information from third party sources (e.g., information from our strategic partners, service providers, or the United States Postal Service). We do this to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our products and services to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

When your FreeWebsite.com account is cancelled (either voluntarily or involuntarily) all of your personally identifiable information is placed in "deactivated" status on our relevant FreeWebsite.com databases. However, deactivation of your account does not mean your personally identifiable information has been deleted from our database entirely. We will retain and use your personally identifiable information as necessary in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements.

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

This Site contains links to other websites. FreeWebsite.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (the one specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at support [@] freewebsite.com.
